<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">iJMC</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string-array name="navigation_items">
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Developers</item>
        <item>Update</item>
        <item>Help</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="main_menu_titles">
        <item>JMC Profile</item>
        <item>Vision, Mission, Goals</item>
        <item>Admin Officials</item>
        <item>Faculty Members</item>
        <item>SSG</item>
        <item>JMC Hymn</item>
        <item>Departments</item>
        <item>Others</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="jmc_content">
        On April 9, 2000, in the hallowed grounds of the five-hectare Kingdom of Jesus Christ compound in Catitipan, Davao City, Rev. Apollo C. Quiboloy, the Founding President, led the ground breaking ceremony of the four-storey educational institution – the JOSE MARIA ACADEMY. This U-shaped building was planned to house first class educational amenities including computer laboratory rooms, audio-visual rooms, chemistry and physics laboratories, speech laboratory, Home Economics room, Math and Science centers, multi-purpose function rooms, fully air-conditioned libraries, offices and classrooms. After passing the qualifications and requirements of the Department of Education (DepEd), the JOSE MARIA ACADEMY, a NON-SECTARIAN SCHOOL, opened the preschool education program until the second grade in the elementary level on June 17, 2002.

In less than a year of operation, last Jan. 24, 2003 the Securities and Exchange Commission approved the conversion of the jmc-hallowed-groundJOSE MARIA ACADEMY to JOSE MARIA COLLEGE. The Commission on Higher Education (CHED) granted the college a permit to operate and offer courses in AB Theology and AB English for school year 2003-2004. From the preschool level, the institution took on its full blast operation as it offered complete elementary and secondary programs in the same school year. For the school year 2004-2005, CHED approved additional courses were approved namely Bachelor of Secondary Education (BSED) major in English and Math, Bachelor of Elementary Education (BEED) major in English and Math, BS Computer Science, and AB Mass Communication. In the same school year 2004-2005, the CHED also granted the school an approval to accept Hearing Impaired (HI) students.

Another five (5) collegiate and two (2) Technical Education Skills Development Authority (TESDA) courses were approved for school year 2005-2006. These are Bachelor of Science in Accountancy (BSA), Bachelor of Science in Civil Engineering (BSCE), Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (BSIT), Bachelor of Science in Psychology (BS Psych), Diploma in Computer Technician (DCT) and Diploma in Computer Science (DCS). DCT and DCS were later changed into 393 Hours Computer Hardware Servicing NC II. jmc-groundsThe Bureau of Immigration gave the school authority to accept foreign students (AAFS No. FZL 05-0015-M(D) last September 8, 2005. Last December 20, 2005, TESDA granted the school authority to operate the 6 Months Caregiver Course. The course was later renamed as 786 Hours Caregiving NC II.

CHED also gave permit to the school to open and conduct the First and Second Years in BS in Commerce (BSC) major in Management Accounting course last January 10, 2006. This course was changed into Bachelor of Science in Business Administration major in Financial Management effective School Year 2007-2008 per CHED Memorandum Order No. 39, Series of 2006. In less than four years of operation, JMC has taken another giant leap when the DepEd granted Government Recognition to its Preschool, Elementary and Secondary programs, while six college courses were recognized by

CHED namely: Bachelor of Arts in Mass Communication (BA MassCom) Bachelor of Arts in English (BA English) Bachelor of Arts in Theology (BA Theology) Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (BSCS) Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (BSIT) Bachelor of Secondary Education (BSEd) majors in English Mathematics and Bachelor of Elementary Education (BEEd)

In the year 2008, Bachelor of Science in Accountancy (BSA) was given governmentjmc-construction-yr-2000 recognition and two years after, in the year 2010 Bachelor of Science in Civil Engineering (BSCE) was likewise recognized by CHED. In the same year Bachelor of Science in Social Work (BSSW) was added to the school’s course offering. The School is also an active member of the following organizations: Association of Private and State Colleges and Universities in Region XI (APSCUR-XI) Private Schools Athletic Association (PRISAA), Asian Association of School HRMD Practitioners, Inc. (AASHPI) Association of Registrars of Schools, Colleges &amp; Universities, Region XI (ARSCU) Davao Private Schools Librarians Association, Inc. (DPSLI) Council of Deans of Engineering Education (CODEE), Council of Deans for Teacher Education Institutions (CODTEI XI) Philippine Association for Teacher Education (PAFTE), Philippine Society of Information Technology Students Council of Deans in Information Technology Education (CDITE), Davao Association of Colleges and Schools (DACS) Fund for Assistance for Private Education (FAPE) Private Education Retirement Annuity Association (PERAA) Junior Social Work Association of the Philippines (JSWAP) Philippine Association of Social Workers Inc.(PASWI) National Association of Social Work Educators Incorporated (NASWEI) Association of Civil Engineering Educators in the Philippines (ACEEP) Academe Industry Tripartite Council (AITC)

It has also established partnership with Indonesian Schools on Educational Programs.
    </string>

</resources>